iwinnersadvantage.com 2014-04-04

# Privacy Policy - I Winners Advantage (IWA)

IWINNERSADVANTAGE.COM

Policy Last Revised: November 29, 2008.

The following sets forth the policies for the collection and use of personally identifiable information (�Information�) by I Online Marketing LLC (�I-Online�) in connection with its operation of its Web site located at http://www.iwinnersadvantage.com (the �Site�), and supersedes any previous statement of such policies. I Online Marketing LLC takes its obligations regarding privacy very seriously, and it wants to ensure users are fully informed about the Information they are providing to it.

Collection of Information.

In connection with the Site, I Online Marketing LLC may collect Information in the following ways:

  * Through forms filled out by a user on the Site
  * Through Information provided by a user in connection with horoscope products, surveys and prize promotion entries
  * Through the maintenance and analysis of Web server logs
  * Via e-mail and other communications between a user and I Online Marketing LLC

I Online Marketing LLC may also connect non-personally identifiable information from users via �cookies� (small text files placed by I Online Marketing LLC on user computers), single-pixel GIF image files (also called �Web beacons�), Web server log analysis and other similar technological means. Such information may be used to track site trends and enhance the user experience, and may be shared with third parties.

To the extent third parties may place advertising on the Site, such third parties may utilize cookies or other technological means within the advertising to collect and utilize non-personally identifiable information. I Online Marketing LLC is not responsible for information collected by third parties in this manner, nor for the collection or use of Information by other sites to which the Site is linked.

Types of Information Collected by I Online Marketing LLC.

The following types of Information about a user are among those that may be collected by I Online Marketing LLC in connection with the Site:

  * Name
  * Postal address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number
  * Cell phone number
  * Age
  * Date of birth
  * Time of birth
  * Place of birth
  * Credit card and other billing information
  * IP Address
  * Referring site
  * Other technical information collected by the Site�s servers.

No Collection of Information from Children.

The Site is not intended for users under the age of 18, nor does I Online Marketing LLC knowingly collect or retain Information in connection with the Site from children under the age of 13.

_Use of Information._

I Online Marketing LLC may use Information collected in connection with the Site in the following ways:

  * To provide requested information, products and services to users via the Site or through other online or offline channels
  * To enable users to enter prize promotions and receive prizes from I Online Marketing LLC and/or third parties
  * To improve the user experience with the Site
  * In connection with the operation of the Site
  * For users to obtain information and offers for products and services offered by I Online Marketing LLC as well as selected third parties.

In order to do the foregoing, I Online Marketing LLC may provide the Information to trusted third parties, including but not limited to selected third party marketers and vendors as well as third party contractors providing services to I Online Marketing LLC such as the operation of the Site, communication services and fulfillment of orders, and information verification. I Online Marketing LLC will use commercially reasonable efforts to limit use of the Information by such third parties to the specific uses set forth above. I Online Marketing LLC also utilizes electronic and physical security to reduce the risk of improper access to or manipulation of Information during transmission and storage, but cannot guarantee the security or integrity of the Information and shall have no liability for breaches of security or integrity or third-party interception in transit.

I Online Marketing LLC may also disclose Information to affiliated entities, when it determines it is necessary to comply with applicable laws or regulations, in connection with a merger, acquisition, asset purchase or sale of or by I Online Marketing LLC, or to protect the interests or safety of I Online Marketing LLC, its customers, or other visitors to the Site.

_Opting Out from Offers from I Online Marketing LLC._

At any time, a user may [opt out](http://www.iwinnersadvantage.com/?p=unsubscribe) from receiving future offers from I Online Marketing LLC through the user�s profile on the Site, by following the instructions contained within each marketing communication. Such opting out will not apply to any communications from third parties to whom I Online Marketing LLC may have provided Information regarding the user. Third parties� use of the Information is subject to such parties� own privacy policies, for which I Online Marketing LLC shall not be responsible.

_Access to Information._

All users who provide their Information to I Online Marketing LLC may modify and correct such Information by contacting I Online Marketing LLC at 570 South Research Drive, Central Islip, NY 17722, USA. IwinnersAdvanatge.com utilizes e-mail as a primary communication channel with customers. As a customer, and by submitting your information on the IwinnersAdvanatge.com website, you hereby acknowledge and grant IwinnersAdvanatge.com the permission to communicate with you via e-mail. IwinnersAdvanatge.com determines to, system messages, confirmation messages, newsletters, service announcements and other promotional messages. IwinnersAdvanatge.com will use best efforts to honor customers requests to [OPTOUT](http://www.iwinnersadvantage.com/?p=unsubscribe) procedures. 

_Your California Privacy Rights._

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of I Online Marketing LLC who are California residents to request certain information regarding I Online Marketing LLC�s disclosure of personal information to third parties for such third parties� direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to 570 South Research Drive, Central Islip, NY 17722, USA.

_Changes to this Privacy Policy._

I Online Marketing LLC reserves the right to revise and update this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such revisions will be effective on the date of posting to the Site, and will apply to all information collected by I Online Marketing LLC both prior to and following the effective date. Your use of the Site following any such revisions will be deemed your acceptance of such revisions. Users should periodically visit this page to review the current policies with regard to Information.
